



Rebeca Freitas Gasso Fraga +55 051 981746172

Rebeca Gasso

SUMMARY

Rebeca is a Software Engineer with six years of software development experience. She started getting interested in web development when was a teen building her own theme for tumblr. She has experience in companies that include Cloud Hosting, E-commerce and Design System. Rebeca focuses on Front-End development, her main technology are React/Typescript and CSS/SASS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Thoughtworks March 2020 - Currently

Consultant Developer

Rebeca works as a software engineer for a clothing department store client. She helps the Foundation team to build and maintain the typescript components library that will be used by other development teams.

Stefanini Brasil July 2019 - January 2020

Software Developer

Rebeca joined Stefanini Brazil to integrate the team, from Dell Inc. client, that would take care of the Rubicon that handles the internal organization of sellers.

Redehost September 2018 - June 2019

Software Developer - internship

Rebeca joined RedeHost to integrate the team that would take care of hosting websites, emails and cloud servers. The team also developed internal systems and web systems.

WebGlobal July 2017 — August 2018

Front-End Developer - internship

Rebeca joined WebGlobal to integrate the team that would build and maintain webapplications. They built the front-end of a price comparison called WebArCondicionado.

VOLUNTEERING

FRC 1772 - The Brazilian Trail Blazers

2021

Programming Mentor

Rebeca was a volunteer mentoring the programming team of the FRC 1772 robotic team. They use JAVA to control the robots.

The Developers Conference

December, 2018

Volunteer Staff

Rebeca worked as volunteer to organize the TDC4Woman track in The Developers Conference Brazil.

Django Girls May, 2019

Coach

Rebeca worked as volunteer at Django Girls, a free Python and Django workshop to women.

EDUCATION

Computer Science 2016 – 2018

Universidade Luterana do Brasil

System Development - Web

January, 2023 - Currently

Universidade do Vale do Rio dos Sinos

Expand knowledge in technological studies of the Internet and all its applications, in addition to understanding the interaction and communication aspects involved in these technologies and their impacts on users.

Biology

January, 2024 - Currently

PUCRS

We train professionals capable of solving problems in a critical and reflective way, who master new technologies and follow social changes, always aiming to conserve biodiversity and socio-environmental sustainability.

SKILLS

Front-end

- HTML5 / CSS3 / Preprocessors
- React.js
- Typescript
- Tailwind
- Material-ui
- Styled-components

Back-end

- ASP.net
- JAVA

Testing technologies

- Cypress
- Jest
- Testing Library
- Playwright

Other technologies

- Git
- Jenkins
- Webpack

Languages

- Português
- English
- Spanish